Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize - Series XI: Art Works, 149056
  - Subseries D: Source/Background Material, 149071
    - New York Post cover, Aug 10 1988 - "Some Cops Hid Badges. .", 149081 (Box XI.23, Folder 21)
    - Print material - "Militant Eroticism Art" calendar, 1990, 149080 (Box XI.23, Folder 22)
    - "Loteria Nacional" tables, undated; 149079 (Folder 25)
    - Commercially Printed: "The Sermon on the Mount", Undated; 149077 (Box XI.24, Folder 20)
    - Patterned paper (handmade?), undated; 149076 (Box XII.46, Folder 8)
    - Comic strip - "Buck missing on Mercury!", undated; 149075 (Box XII.46, Folder 13)
    - Pumpkin cutout, undated; 149074 (Box XII.46, Folder 7)
    - Paper bag with logo: "I (heart) America;" Poster with logo and spray paint: "British Airways/London Bridge", undated; 149073 (Box XII.46, Folder 11)
    - Indian style painting, possibly Thangka center painted panel, undated (Box XII.46, Folder 14)
    - 16 supermarket advertisements and one map of the USA, Undated; 092.2.105; 17 items 16 posters and one map (Object 092.2.105)
      Posters.
  - Subseries E: Plans, 149068
    - Notes, sketches, and plans for artworks, Undated; 149070 (Box XI.24, Folder 4)
    - Notes and Sketches: "Lists & Ideas for Work", Undated; 149069 (Box XI.24, Folder 3)
  - Subseries F: Xerox Art, 149065
    - Photostat: [Romulus and Remus myth: two infants with wolf], Undated (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Photocopies of drawings: face with sewn lips (1); Face with sewn lips with brick wall background (3); brick wall (1), Undated; 149067 (Box XI.24, Folder 16)
    - Color Photocopy composition (skeleton, baby, snowflake, fabric), Undated; 149066 (Box XI.24, Folder 15)
  - Subseries G: Other People's Art, 149057
    - Poster, silkscreened: "Did you ever want to kill your boss", undated; 149064 (Box XII.46, Folder 4)
    - Barbara Kruger, "Aqui!" Issue 1, Set 1, 1984, 149063 (Box XI.24, Folder 12)
    - Poster/Flyer/Zine: "Evolution of a Masterpiece", Undated; 149061 (Box XI.24, Folder 18)
    - Photo of Michael Roman Poster, "The Jimmies" (NYC summer 1984), 149060 (Box XII.46, Folder 5)
    - Screenprint-"Don't Labor Under a Misconception" (Creator Unknown, (Not DW)), Undated; 149058 (Box XI.24, Folder 17)
    - Jenny Holzer, "Inflammatory Essays", 277366 (Box 98)
    - Kiki Smith, Handmade Photobook, "Dear David...", 1991 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Luis Frangella, Screenprint, "To David", 1983 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified artworks and page of newspaper comics (none D.W.), Undated (Box XI.24, Folder 6)
- Oversize - Series XII: Library, 148224
  Wojnarowicz Library List (note: Photography books may have originally belonged to Peter Hujar.)
  Most titles have been cataloged and can be retrieved by searching Bobcat, the Bobst library's online catalog.
  - Animals from Life. Chicago: Rand, McNally and Co.: 1900. [39], 148276 (Box XII.36, Folder 40)
  - Bacou, Roseline. Piranesi. Berlin: Rembrandt Verlag, 1975., 148275 (Box XII.36, Folder 82)
  - Bomb. No. 8, 1983/84. / Winter 1987., 148274 (Box XII.36, Folder 119)
  - Cordry, Donald. Mexican Masks. Austin: University of Texas Press, 1980., 148273 (Box XII.36, Folder 193)
  - Cover: Arts New York. Janury 1988., 148272 (Box XII.36, Folder 194)
  - Daily News. 11 Dec. 1989, 148271 (Box XII.37, Folder 201)
  - Grosz, George. Ecce Homo. Secaucus, NJ: Castle Books, 1965., 148270 (Box XII.37, Folder 296)
  - Hensley, Tim. Steam, Steel, and Stars. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1987., 148269 (Box XII.37, Folder 327)
  - Holldobler, Bert and Edward O. Wilson. The Ants. Cambridge, MA: Harvard UP, 1990., 148268 (Box XII.38, Folder 335)
  - La Argentina. Buenos Aires: Guillermo Kraft Limitada, 1864., 1964; 148267 (Box XII.38, Folder 393)
  - Les Animaux D'Apres Nature. Paris: E. Bernard, 1905., 148266 (Box XII.39, Folder 404)
  - New York Native. Issue 329. 7 Aug. 1989, 148265 (Box XII.39, Folder 517)
  - New York Newsday. 11 Dec. 1989, 148264 (Box XII.39, Folder 518)
  - ---. 17 Jan. 1991, 148263 (Box XII.39, Folder 519)
  - ---. 21 Jan. 1991, 148262 (Box XII.39, Folder 520)
  - ---. 22 Jan. 1991, 148261 (Box XII.39, Folder 521)
  - ---. 24 Jan. 1991, 148260 (Box XII.40, Folder 522)
  - ---. 25 Jan. 1991, 148259 (Box XII.40, Folder 523)
  - ---. 29 Jan. 1991, 148258 (Box XII.40, Folder 524)
  - ---. 18 March 1991., 148257 (Box XII.40, Folder 525)
  - New York Post. 11 Dec. 1989, 148256 (Box XII.40, Folder 526)
  - ---. 14 June 1990., 148255 (Box XII.40, Folder 527)
  - ---. 18 June 1990., 148254 (Box XII.40, Folder 528)
  - ---. 17 Jan. 1991, 148253 (Box XII.40, Folder 529)
  - ---. 22 Feb. 1991, 148252 (Box XII.40, Folder 530)
  - ---. 7 March 1991., 148251 (Box XII.40, Folder 531)
  - ---. 14 Jan. 1991, 148250 (Box XII.41, Folder 532)
  - ---. 29 Jan. 1991, 148249 (Box XII.41, Folder 533)
  - ---. 20 April 1992., 148248 (Box XII.41, Folder 534)
  - O'Nirem, Dan. El mundo desconocido del amazonas. Caparra Terrace, Puerto Rico: Express Prints, 1983., 148247 (Box XII.41, Folder 539)
  - The Outlook. 25 July 1990., 148246 (Box XII.41, Folder 545)
  - Paper. March 1989., 148245 (Box XII.41, Folder 553)
  - Pieter Bruegel. New York: Harry N. Abrams Inc, 1969. [with inserts], 148244 (Box XII.41, Folder 573)
  - Pronto: US Retail & Trend Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 5 May 1985., 148243 (Box XII.41, Folder 588)
  - Rand McNally Road Atlas. Boston: Rand McNally & Co., 1991., 148242 (Box XII.42, Folder 595)
  - Singh, Raghubir. Calcutta. London: Thames and Hudson, 1988., 148241 (Box XII.42, Folder 643)
  - Stechow, Wolfgang. Pieter Bruegel the Elder. New York: Harry N. Abrams, [n. d]. [source material see pages 13 and 15. ], undated; 148240 (Box XII.42, Folder 657)
  - Steiglitz, Alfred. Georgia O'Keefe. New York: Metropolitan Museum of Modern Art, 1978., 148239 (Box XII.42, Folder 658)
  - Ward, Lynd. Storyteller without Words. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1974., 148238 (Box XII.43, Folder 715)
  - West Sussex Gazette. 13 May 1993., 148237 (Box XII.43, Folder 721)
  - Wingrove, David. The Immortals of Science Fiction. New York: Mayflower Books, 1980., 148236 (Box XII.43, Folder 731)
  - Ambrosius, Ernst and Konrad Frenzel. Das Bild der Erde. Bielefeld: Velhagen & Klafing, 1930., 148235 (Box XII.44, Folder 29)
  - Arader III, W. Graham. Native Grace. Charlottesville, VI: Thomasson-Grant, 1988., 148234 (Box XII.45, Folder 46)
  - Express. [K 2 Aug. 1986, 148233 (Box XII.44, Folder 249)
  - ---. [K 2 Sept. 1986, 148232 (Box XII.44, Folder 250)
  - The Voice. 26 June 1990., 148231 (Box XII.44, Folder 710)
  - National Geographic Atlas of the World. Washington D. C.: National Geographic Society, 1963, 148230 (Box XII.45, Folder 498)
  - Standard Atlas of Ford Country. Chicago: Geo. A. Ogle and Co., 1916., 148229 (Box XII.45, Folder 653)
  - State Farm Road Atlas. Bloomington, IL: The State Farm Insurance Co., 1939., 148228
  - East Village Eye. Vol. V, No. 36, September 1983. /Vol. V, No. 53, May 1984. /Vol. VIII, No. 61, Dec/Jan 1986. /Vol. VIII, No. 63, March 1986., 148227 (Box XII.46, Folder 744)
  - Distributed Art Publishers, Catalogs, Spring 1992/Fall 1992., 148226 (Box XII.46, Folder 745)
  - Publication: "Your House is Mine, An Act of Resistance 1988-1992." New York: Bullet Space, 1993, 1988-1993; 148225 (Box XII.46, Folder 9)
- Mapcase - Series VII: Subjects, 149051
  - Subseries C: Announcements, 149052
    - Argentina Posters, undated; 232208 (Folder 19)
    - "Cop Shoot Cop," Tues Apr 4, Pyramid; "Rock Barricada," Danceteria, April 1, undated; 149055 (Folder 8 Right)
    - "Harry Kondoleon / Poet's Corner" Poster, undated; 232206 (Folder 9 Right)
    - "Holidays in the Sun" (The Sex Pistols) Poster, undated; 149054 (Folder 20)
    - "Larry Clark and Peter Hujar, Frankfurter Kunstverein" Posters, undated; 232210 (Folder 10 Right)
    - "Retrospective Posters", undated; 232216 (Folder 21)
    - "Silence = Death" / "Positive" Film Screening Poster, undated; 232214 (Folder 11 Right)
    - Spanish-language Posters & Rose-Patterned Wrapping Paper, undated; 232209 (Folder 22)
    - "Ueber Sofa Auf die Strasse!" Poster, undated; 232212 (Folder 12 Right)
    - Various Cultural & Political Posters, undated; 149053 (Folder 13 Right)
- Mapcase - Series XI: Art Works, 149039
  - Subseries A: Finished/Original, 149047
    - "Democracy", undated; 232197 (Folder 4 Right)
    - "Hunger", undated; 232226 (Folder 7 Right)
    - Offset Plates - "Between C & D", "A Few Months Ago...", undated; 232221 (Folder 17)
    - Poster for "Electric Messages Beneath the Sea," Brigitte Engler, The Parallel Window; metal template for "Between C&D" poster, undated; 149049 (Folder 18)
    - "Psychiatric Clinic, Court of General Sessions", by David Wojnarowicz and Kiki Smtih, undated; 232207 (Map-case 1.J, Folder 15)
    - "Romulus and Remus Silkscreen Pt. 1", undated; 232200 (Folder 6 Right)
    - "Snowflakes - White, Snowman - Dark" Double Lithograph, undated; 232215 (Folder 16)
    - Stencil Tool: Skeleton with Pope Hat, undated; 232198 (Folder 1 Left, Folder 17 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Bug, undated (Folder 2 Left)
    - Stencil Tool: Flames with Gorilla, Undated (Folder 14 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Wolf/Dog Head, undated (Folder 15 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Abstract Animal Face, undated (Folder 16 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Pebble Pattern, undated (Folder 18 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Gorilla Tied to Fence, undated (Folder 19 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Man's Profile Smoking with Grass, undated (Folder 20 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Man's Profile, undated (Folder 20 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Outline of Couple Kissing, undated (Folder 21 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Couple Kissing, undated (Folder 22 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Monkey, undated (Folder 23 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Couple Kissing - small, undated (Folder 24 Right)
    - Stencil Image: Falling Man and Map of U.S.A., 1982 (Folder 3 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Skeleton with Pope Hat, undated (Folder 4 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Barbed Wire, undated (Folder 6 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Man Fighting Bull, undated (Folder 7 Left)
    - Stencil Image: "I Wanted One of These Things", undated (Folder 8 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Soldier Image with Gun, undated (Folder 9 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Fork, Knife, Plate, undated (Folder 10 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Fork, Knife, Plate with Figure, undated (Folder 10 Left)
    - Stencil Tool and Image: Man's Profile Smoking with Grass, undated (Folder 20 Right)
    - Stencil Tool and Image: Couple Kissing, undated (Folder 21 Right)
    - Stencil Collage: Folded Arm, undated (Folder 5 Left)
    - Stencil Collage: "3 Teens Kill 4 - No Motive", undated (Folder 11 Left)
    - Rough sketches, undated (Folder 12 Left)
    - Boards with no images, undated (Folder 13 Left)
    - Various supermarket posters, undated; 149048 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Various supermarket posters (some altered), undated; 149050 (Folder 15)
  - Subseries D: Source/Background Material, 149044
    - Source: Bullseye targets; anatomical charts of fish and chicken, undated; 149046 (Folder 1 Left, Folder 2 Left, Folder 14)
    - Source: Two Circus posters w/ tigers; poster, "Anatomical Chart of the Acupressure Points" (altered); poster: tribesmen shooting arrows; fragment of evil clowns poster, undated; 149045 (Folder 23)
    - Source: Spanish-language posters (3), poster: "The Un-Work Force", undated; 271997 (Map-case 1.J, Folder 22a)
  - Subseries E: Plans, 149042
    - "Vaccinate Your God", undated; 149043 (Folder 3 Left)
  - Subseries G: Other People's Art, 149040
    - Kiki Smith, "Cause I'm on My Own Time," 4/28/84, 1984; 149041 (Folder 24)
- Series XIV: Accretions 2001 - Media, 148214
  - VHS: David Wojnarowicz text voice-over, Fear of Disclosure material [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated; 148223 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure dancer source material [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated; 148222 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - VHS: David Wojnarowicz speech at memorial service for Phil Zwickler 6/1/91 [Estate Project/NYPL], 1991; 148221 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure source materials - David Wojnarowicz images 11/1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], 148220 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure, David Wojnarowicz and Phil Zwickler 1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], 148219 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure, Phil Zwickler and David Wojnarowicz text [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated; 148218 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure text - source material 8/1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], 148217 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Audiocassette Sony 90: Interview w/ David Wojnarowicz by Adam Kuby 9/14/91 [Gift of Adam Kuby 6/29/01], 1991; 148216 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - DAT: JAG #258-Where Evil Dwells., undated; 148215 (Box 147, Folder 9)
- Series VI: Accretions 2001 - Biographical, 148204
  - Subseries E: Taxes, Receipts, and Legal Documents, 148205
    - Correspondence re: Wojnarowicz Published Works and Visual Arts, undated; 148213 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 1)
    - Estate Appraisal by P. P. O. W., undated; 148212 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 2)
    - Freedman and Fish Correspondence re: Will and Last Testament, undated; 148211 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 3)
    - Will and Last Testament, undated; 148210 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 4)
    - Legal Documents, undated; 148209 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 5)
    - Legal Documents, undated; 148208 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, undated; 148207 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 7)
    - 16 mm Reel-JAG #240 and #255-Where Evil Dwells., undated; 148206 (Box VI.E.3, Folder no number)
- Accretions 2003, 278740
  - Notes by David, 1992; 278741 (Box 99)
  - Various documents, undated; 278809 (Box 99)
  - Plaintiff Exhibit 9: Tongues of Flame, 1990; 278810 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Plaintiff's Exhibits: David Wojnarowicz vs. American Family Association and Donald E. Wildmon, 1990; 278811 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Posthumous print materials, 2002; 278812
  - Personal and Art photographs, ca. 1970 - 1992; 278813 (Box 100)
    Inlcudes self portrait photobooth photos, snapshots from France, photos from the Westside piers, polaroids of David in his studio, portraits of David by Peter Hujar, Eric Kroll and others, polaroids of Tom and David, polaroids of stenciled works, etc.
  - Photographs, 278814 (Box 101)
- Unprocessed Accretion (Box 171, Box 172, Box 173)